lucyinthesky.com 2012-12-20

# Privacy policy

PRIVACY POLICY

References in this Privacy Policy Statement to

"we", "us" and "Lucy in the Sky" are to Lucy in

the Sky online store Pty Ltd. At Lucy in the Sky we are committed to

maintaining your privacy. Our privacy policy statement is given below. If we

make changes to this policy, we will notify you by updating this statement on

our Website.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We ask for your name, telephone number, home address, email address and age for

competitions, prizedraws, or newsletter sign ups. When a purchase is made on

our site, in addition to the above, we also ask for delivery address, and

payment method details. We may obtain information about your usage of our

Website to help us develop and improve it further through online surveys and

other requests.

WHAT THE DATA WILL BE USED FOR?

Your data will enable us, and our processors, to fulfil your order, to notify

you about important functionality changes and for statistical or survey

purposes to improve this website and our services to you. We may also send you

from time to time (by email or post) information about products and services

and details of promotions and special offers from Lucy in the Sky. If you do

not wish to be contacted for these purposes, we offer a range of ways in which

you can inform us about your marketing preferences:

•    All email messages and email newsletters will contain

information on how you can unsubscribe; or

•    Call our customer service on 02 4325 0003 or if calling

from overseas on +61 2 4325 0003.

•    Write to us at: Customer Service, Lucy in the Sky, Level 1,  120 Erina Street, Gosford NSW 2250

Australia.

In assessing your request for goods or services, we may use your information

for the purposes of the prevention and detection of fraud.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE SHARE WITH OTHERS?

We may contract with other companies to provide certain services, including

credit card processing, shipping, name and address verification, email

distribution, market research and promotions management. We provide these

companies with only the information they need to perform their services and

work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected.

These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for

their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other

than Lucy in the Sky. We may disclose specific information upon governmental

request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may

also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or

investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for

marketing or commercial purposes.

COOKIES

A Cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your

computer. We use Cookies to keep track of your current shopping session, to

enable you to proceed to checkout at any time and to personalize your online

experience. If you do not accept Cookies you will be unable to use this website.

Refer to the Help content of your browser for more information on selecting or

deselecting Cookies.

LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES SITES

In an attempt to provide you with increased

value, we may from time to time include third party links on our Website. These

linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We encourage you

to review those policies when you visit those sites. This Privacy Policy

Statement only covers our Website and does not cover any other website. We

therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of

these linked sites.

PRIVACY OF CHILDREN ON OUR WEBSITE

Our Website is not intended for use by children

under the age of 14, and we will not knowingly collect any information from any

person below the age of 14.

SALE OF ASSETS

In the unlikely event that Lucy in the Sky or

substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of

course be one of the transferred assets.
